extremefunnelmakeover.com 2017-09-28

# Privacy Policy Notice - ClickFunnels

**I. Personally-Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information.**

Etison, LLC (also referred to herein as “ClickFunnels”) may collect two different types of information, Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”) and Non-Personally Identifiable Information (“Non-PII”). PII is information that identifies you as an individual – for example, your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card information, billing address and shipping information. Non-PII is aggregated information, demographic information, IP addresses, user behavior data from web interaction metrics tools and other information that does not reveal your specific identity. PII and Non-PII may be collected anytime you access or use a ClickFunnels website. PII and Non-PII may also be collected by ClickFunnels during in-person discussions, telephone conversations, and electronic or other written communications. ClickFunnels also collects information via cookies; blocking cookies may render you unable to access certain ClickFunnels products, services, or websites.

ClickFunnels uses PII to respond to your inquiries, provide you with services you have requested, keep you informed of services ClickFunnels thinks may be of interest to you, and otherwise personalize your experience with ClickFunnels, and other reasons. ClickFunnels does not sell or lease PII about you to others. ClickFunnels may share PII with ClickFunnels affiliates and third parties contracting with ClickFunnels to provide services to you, e.g., financial institutions. ClickFunnels may also share PII when required by law, or when you have expressly requested ClickFunnels to do so. ClickFunnels reserves the right to disclose and use your PII if ClickFunnels believes it is necessary to: (a) respond to legal process, e.g., a subpoena; (b) respond to a law enforcement agency’s request; (c) enforce the Terms; or (d) protect the rights, privacy, safety, property, or operations of ClickFunnels or third parties;

Because Non-PII does not personally identify You, ClickFunnels reserves the right to use and disclose to third parties Non-PII for any purpose.

ClickFunnels maintains reasonable physical, administrative and technical safeguards to protect PII from loss, misuse, or unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. ClickFunnels enforces its Privacy Policy via self-assessment.

ClickFunnels reserves the right to change this privacy notice, which changes will become effective upon posting of the revised notice https://www.clickfunnels.com/privacy, or upon emailing of the changes to You at the email address You provided to ClickFunnels, or as required by law.

**II. Links to or From Other Sites.**

Except where expressly stated by ClickFunnels, ClickFunnels is not affiliated or associated with operators of any third party websites that link to or are linked from any ClickFunnels-maintained website. ClickFunnels disclaims any responsibility for the accuracy or content of information found on third party websites that link to or are linked from any ClickFunnels website. ClickFunnels disclaims any responsibility for the security of any information (including without limitation credit card and personally identifiable information (“PII”)) that you may provide to any third party. ClickFunnels reserves the right, at any time and in its sole and absolute discretion, to block links to any ClickFunnels-maintained website through technological or other means without prior notice.

**III. Information; Registration; User Names and Passwords**

As a ClickFunnels website user, You will be required to create an account with ClickFunnels. You warrant that the information you provide ClickFunnels is truthful and accurate, and that you are not impersonating another person. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of any password you may use to access your ClickFunnels account, and you agree not to transfer your password or User name, or lend or otherwise transfer your use of or access to your account, to any third party. You are fully responsible for all transactions with, and information conveyed to, ClickFunnels under your account. You agree to immediately notify ClickFunnels of any unauthorized use of your password or User name or any other breach of security related to your account. You agree that ClickFunnels is not liable, and you will hold ClickFunnels harmless, for any loss or damage arising from your failure to comply with any of the foregoing obligations.

**IV. Release/Authorization to Use Photographs.**

You grant ClickFunnels permission to use any and all photographs, or video or audio or digital recordings, taken by ClickFunnels or its agents or employees, or submitted by You to ClickFunnels (hereinafter “Photographs”) in any Media (including print, internet, film, television and no matter how distributed or published) for any purpose, which may include, but shall not be limited to, advertising, promotion, marketing and packaging of ClickFunnels or any product or service sold and marketed by ClickFunnels. You agree that this authorization to use Photographs may be assigned by ClickFunnels to any other party. You agree that that the Photographs may be combined with other Photographs, sounds, text and graphics, and that the Photographs may be manipulated, cropped, altered or modified in ClickFunnels’ sole discretion. You agree not to charge a royalty or fee, and not to make any other monetary assessment against ClickFunnels in exchange for this Release and Assignment. You hereby release and forever discharge ClickFunnels from any and all liability and from any damages you may suffer as a result of the use of the Photographs. You further acknowledge and agree that this Release is binding upon your heirs and assigns. You agree that this Release is irrevocable.
